翻译：Iz      Tiogy      红豆包      小布拿拿
校对&总监：Iz
后期：斯人     时间轴：深夏桃子
更多动画  就在@欧美动漫汉化军团
《开心汉堡店》第五季第十三集
裤子里没有蚂蚁[俗语"裤子里有蚂蚁"形容人焦虑或激动]
除虫害公司
这座椅被我转出了一种新声音
Hey, this stool is making a new sound when I spin on it.
介于动物海豹
It's somewhere right between seal the animal
和歌手海豹[英国R&B歌手]的声音之间
and Seal the amazing singer.
我会买这椅子的专辑
I'd buy that stool's album.
不许取乐  你们还在禁足中
No having fun. You kids are grounded.
我有件有趣的事
Here's something fun.
我需要有人去帮我把老油倒了
I need someone to run the old grease out to the Dumpster.
别那样说老妈
Don't talk about Mom that way.
老妈  你还在生气吗
Mom, are you still mad?
你都关我们四小时的禁闭了
You grounded us four hours ago.
我们现在比那时成熟好多了
We've grown so much since then.
是的  我还在生气
Yes. I'm still mad.
而且我会一直生气下去
And I'm gonna be mad about it forever.
但今天是周末啊
But it's the weekend.
今天该去伯尼家的[连锁零售商店]
Everybody's supposed to go to Bernie's!
-好啦  琳  我知道你  -不行
- Come on, Lin. I-I know you... - No!
-我能  -不想谈
- Can I just... - Not talking about it.
-琳  -永远不谈
- L-Lin. - Ever.
盖尔姨妈来了
Here comes Aunt Gayle.
我知道这么说挺扯淡
And I know this sounds crazy,
但她看起来好像在哭哎
but she looks like she's crying.
天哪  她不会进来吧
Oh, God. She can't just stop by, can she?
咱们应该备一间避难室
Why don't we have a panic room?
我的人生完了
Well, my life is ruined.
-天哪  -怎么了
- Oh, God. - What's wrong?
琳达  还记得我在猫吧遇到的那个人吗
Oh, Linda, you remember that guy I met on Cat Chat?
-叫史黛西那个  -记得
- Stacy? - Yeah...
等等  男人也能叫史黛西么
Wait, men can be named Stacy?
我爱美国
I love America!
我们本来要去猫戏团的
Well, we were supposed to go see Yarnival...
有点像太阳马戏团  但表演的都是猫
it's like Cirque du Soleil but with cats...
结果他取消计划了
and then he canceled.
那我只能带上鲍勃了
So I guess I'll take Bob.
不行  不行  不行
No. No, no, no. No. J... No.
我和你去  盖尔姨妈
I'll go with you, Aunt Gayle.
我们早就该培养培养感情了
We've been meaning to hang out for ages
但一直没能抽出时间  对吧
but couldn't make our calendars work, remember?
不  带上我吧  我超想看猫戏团
No, take me! I yearn for yarn.
拜托了  盖尔  我需要呼吸外面的空气
Please, Gayle! I need to breathe outside air!
我需要触摸到风
I need to touch the wind!
你们还真是很想和我一起玩呢
You guys really want to hang out with me.
那是因为他们被我关禁闭了
They only want to go 'cause they're grounded.
他们为什么被关了禁闭
Why are they grounded?
没有理由  看我心情
No reason! I just felt like it.
他们不能出去
They're not allowed to go.
好吧
Okay, fine.
我自己去  没关系的
I'll go by myself. That's okay.
等我孤零零死掉的时候
I can use the empty seat next to me
还可以倒在旁边的椅子上
to slump into when I die alone!
好吧
All right, fine.
你可以带走一个
One of them can go.
带哪个随便你
I don't care which one.
他们每个都很讨厌
They're all equally terrible.
等一等
Hold up there.
你得让我们用比赛决胜负
You have to let us compete for it.
赌上性命
To the death.
不  不要提死  露易丝
No. No death, Louise.
或者我们可以
Or we could, I don't know, maybe go by,
比谁的小鸡鸡最大
who has the biggest ding dong.
吉恩
Gene.
不  我来告诉你们比什么
No. I'll tell you what you're gonna do.
比你们讨厌做的事
You're gonna do something you hate.
-我想想  你们讨厌什么呢  -玉米片
- Let me see. What do you hate? - Nachos?
家庭作业  就它了
Homework. That's what you're gonna do.
做数学题
You're gonna do math.
我们可以写作文
Or we could write essays.
-你竟敢  -想都别想
- How dare you. - Never!
多棒的主意呀  蒂娜  我喜欢
What a great idea, Tina. I love it.
鉴于票在我手里
Since I'm the one with the tickets,
我希望作文的主题是我
I want the essays to be about me!
我想要动作  冒险  爱情  戏剧
I want action, adventure, love, drama.
还有斯科特・巴库拉[美国演员]
And Scott Bakula.
-天哪  -好啦  你们听到姨妈的话了
- Oh, God. - All right, you heard the lady.
现在  开始
Your time starts... now!
三十分钟后
时间到  停笔
And time. Pencils down.
好吧  谁先来  谁来念
Okay, who's up? Who's gonna read?
我先来  因为我鸡鸡最大
I'll go first because I have the biggest ding dong!
-吉恩  -我的故事名叫
- Gene. - My story is called
"盖尔与乔・吉恩之歌"
"The Ballad of Gayle and Jo Gene."
听时请准备手帕和厕纸
And I hope you brought your hankies and some toilet paper,
因为本故事要么催人泪下  要么全程尿点
'cause there's not gonna be a dry eye or butt in the house.
故事发生在  田纳西州的那什维尔
The place: Nashville, Tennessee.
这是一个闷热的夜晚
It was a hot, sweaty night, and the patrons
旅途之琴酒吧的常客们
at the Fiddle of the Road Saloon
都迫不及待地要听他们最爱的
couldn't wait to hear their favorite act,
琳戴特和乔・吉恩的演出
Lindette and Jo Gene.
他们光彩耀人  让你忍不住大喊"太棒啦"
They had the glitz and glam to make you say, "Hot damn!"
拉娜喜欢大羊驼  但大羊驼喜欢睡衣
Lana loves a llama, but the llama loves pajamas.
绕口令
你会唱得很好的  琳戴特
Y'all sound great, Lindette.
我必须唱好
I better.
卢・贝尔彻拉坐在台下呢
Lou Belchera is here,
她是好莱坞最棒的歌手经纪人
the big fancy Hollywood singing agent.
所以千万别给我搞砸了
So don't screw it up for me.
一  二  一  二  三  四
A-one, a-two, a-one, two, three, four.
*州长有一头小猪*
*Oh, the sheriff had a piggy *
*神经不正常*
*And he was mighty mad *
*他看到我来  一口叼走了我的香肠*
*He saw me a-coming and my wiener he did grab *
*我放声大哭  感觉人生毫无意义*
*Now I can't quit cryin' and life just ain't no fun *
*一只肥狗吃了我的热狗*
*'Cause a fat dog ate my hot dog *
*除了一块小面包  我一无所有  *
*And I got nothin' but the bun. *Yeehaw!
孩子们
Hi, kids.
我是卢・贝尔彻拉  好莱坞歌手经纪人
I'm Lou Belchera, Hollywood singing agent,
我就直说吧
and I'm gonna cut to the chase.
我很喜欢你刚才的演出
I like what you did out there.
非常喜欢  我想让你成为我的签约歌手
I liked it a lot. And I'd like you to be my client
参加下周五的奥普里歌唱比赛
and compete in the Big Ole Opry sing-off next Friday.
你觉得怎么样
What do you say?
我们求之不得
We say yes!
不  不是你  矮冬瓜
No, not you, fumble weed.
我是指这位长着一对儿翘臀的高个儿
The tall one with the big yams.
不好意思  但我们是二人组
I'm sorry, but we're a duo.
不  我要单飞了
No! I'm going solo!
-等等  什么  不行  -行
- Wait, what? No. - Yes!
行  行  行  行
Yes, yes, yes, yes!
*行*
*Yes... *
但是我怎么办
But what about me?!
什么怎么办  你没听她说吗
What about you? You heard her.
我是明星了
I'm a star.
不  你目前还不是  小姐
No, not yet, you aren't, lady.
但如果你赢了明晚的比赛
But if you win the big sing-off tomorrow night,
我就会带你去好莱坞  给你一幢公寓
I'll take you to Hollywood and give you a mansion
并把你介绍给...
and introduce you to,
斯科特・巴库拉先生好了
I don't know, Mr. Scott Bakula?
太好啦  你出去  乔・吉恩
Yay! Get out of here, Jo Gene.
我现在已经是一颗彩虹莱茵石
I'm like a rhinestone rainbow
而你还是一箱臭湿鞋
and you're like a trunk full of wet boots.
好吧  但是我要拿走剩余的冷盘
Fine! But I'm taking the rest of the cold cuts!
还有我的亮片抹胸
And my sequin tube top!
还有我的梦想
And my dreams!
还有意大利甜椒
And the pepperoncinis!
爱拿什么拿什么吧  你这只头猪
Take whatever you want, you little pig.
还有蔬菜色拉
And the crudites.
你敢碰蔬菜色拉
Don't you touch that crudites!
这是我的
It's mine!
一杯热巧克力  加沙士
Shot of hot fudge with a root beer back.
瓶子留下
Leave the bottle.
今晚不好过  是吧
Tough night, huh?
-我的搭档抛下我自己高升了  -天哪
- My singin' partner up and left me. - Oh, man.
我搭档15年前就抛下我高升去了
My singin' partner up and left me 15 years ago.
那又怎么样  我照样过得有声有色
But look at me now. I'm doing great!
又来了
Here it comes.
-我去  -盖尔
- Oh, God. - Gayle!
来把这堆吐的弄干净
Come clean up this throw-up.
*他的车上有口红*
*There's lipstick on his pickup *
*方向盘上有睫毛膏*
*There's mascara on the wheels *
*我看了看杂物箱*
*I looked inside the glove box *
*还有一只红色高跟鞋*
*And I found a red high heel. *
我的天呀
Well, pinch my loaf.
那姑娘真能唱
That girl can sing.
那歌喉[pipe又可指"水管"]
Those pipes you got sound like
像天赐一般
they came straight from heaven.
厕所水管吗  抱歉又堵了
The bathroom pipes? Sorry they're clogged.
总有人往里面扔卫生巾
People keep putting tampons down 'em.
连水池都有人扔
Even the sinks.
不  不  我是说你的歌喉
No, no. I meant your pipes.
用来唱歌的那个
Your singing ones.
我叫乔・吉恩
My name's Jo Gene,
正在寻找新的唱歌搭档
and I'm looking for a new singing partner.
我不是歌手
I'm not really a singer.
我只是个美丽的服务员
I'm just a beautiful waitress
负责清理酒吧里的呕吐物
who cleans up throw-ups in a bar.
现在不是了
Not anymore you're not.
我们先去24小时营业的莱茵石商店吧
Let's get you to the all-night Rhinestone Warehouse quick.
奥普里大剧院[美国广播节目Grand Ole Opry的工作室]
比赛当晚
绕口令
这可笑的鸵鸟有双巨大的脚
The preposterous ostrich's legs were monstrous.
萨利・斯特拉瑟[美国演员]的兄弟是她妈
Sally Struthers' other brother's her mother.
怎么样啊  前搭档
Well, howdy, former pardner.
乔・吉恩  你怎么在这儿
Wha? What are you doing here, Jo Gene?
我是来和我的新搭档拿冠军的
I came here to win with my new partner!
奖牌已经妥妥地在我们的口袋里了
We've got this in the bag.
但不是这个口袋
But not this bag I'm holding,
这里面装的是我的三明治
because that has my sandwich in it!
-滚出去  -别冲着眼睛啊
- Get out of here! - Not my eyes!
我还要测视力呢
I need them for eye exams!
喂  工作人员
Hey. Stage girl.
-怎么了  -帮我把响尾蛇
- Yes? - I need you to put a rattlesnake
放进某人的吉它里
into someone's guitar for me.
好的  女士
Yes, ma'am.
*我要*
*I'll... *
*用这些眼泪跟你换几杯啤酒*
*Trade you these tears for a couple of beers*
*用这些鼻涕换瓶威士忌*
*And this snot for a shot of whiskey... *
她还真不错
Oh, she's good.
是的  她一直很厉害
Yeah. She's real good.
*太欢愉*
*...too frisky. *
掌声献给琳戴特
Let's hear it for Lindette!
下面有请全新的双人组合
Now a brand-new duo.
他曾是琳戴特的搭档
He used to be Lindette's partner,
而她曾是酒吧里清理呕吐物的服务生
and she used to be a waitress who cleaned up throw-ups.
让我们热烈欢迎盖尔和乔・吉恩
Let's give a big Nashville welcome to Gayle and Jo Gene!
这首歌名叫"我不愿让你一个人"
We call this one "I Won't Go Solo on You."
*我想要上厕所*
*Well, I got to use the restroom *
*却没有两人的坑*
*But there ain't a stall for two *
*快挤进来憋住气*
*So squeeze on in and don't breathe in *
*因为我不愿让你一个人*
*'Cause I won't go solo on you *
我吉它里好像有条蛇
I think there's a snake in my guitar.
用上它
Use it.
*我想吃意大利面*
*Well, I'd like to eat spaghetti *
*你却想吃咖喱肉*
*But you want vindaloo *
*于是我马上去点咖喱*
*So I'll leave in a hurry and order some curry *
*因为我不愿让你一个人*
*'Cause I won't go solo on you *
*我和你*
*Oh, you and me *
*永远不分离*
*We're together through and through *
*如果你搬去中国*
*So if you move to China *
*我也会跟着你*
*I'll be right behind ya *
*因为我不愿让你一个人*
*'Cause I won't go solo on you. *
冠军是
And the winner is...
盖尔和乔・吉恩
Gayle and Jo Gene!
-和那条奇怪的蛇  -啥  那是我的蛇啊
- And that wacky snake! - What? That's my snake!
冠军应该是我  我的脸
I should win! Oh, my face!
于是卢・贝尔彻拉签了他们
So Lou Belchera signed them
带他们去好莱坞
and took them to Hollywood,
参观了好莱坞标志  还见了斯科特・巴库拉
where they saw the Hollywood Sign and met Scott Bakula!
每当我难过的时候
I come to the second "O" In the Hollywood sign
就会来标志的第二个"O"这里
when I'm feeling sad,
不过  遇到你好开心
but, oh, boy, am I glad I met you.
琳戴特最后嫁给了酒吧里那个酒鬼
And Lindette ended up married to the old drunk from the bar
因为她是个刻薄的人  爱关别人禁闭
because she was a mean person who liked grounding people
还喜欢单飞
and going solo.
疯子
Nuts.
完了
The end.
我太喜欢这故事了  吉恩
Oh, I just loved it, Gene!
-我不喜欢  逊毙了  -吉恩  你赢了
- Well, I hated it. Boo. - You win, Gene!
*我不愿让你一个人*
*I won't go solo on you *
来吧  我们走
Come on! Let's go!
-等等  -我的故事呢
- Wait! - What about my story?
还有更重要的  我的故事呢
And more importantly, my story.
哦  对
Oh, right, right.
我的故事名叫"查特蒂夫人的情人"
My story is called "Lady Chatterteeth's Lover."
查特蒂姐妹是年华不再 码头
The sisters Chatterteeth were the most beautiful sisters
最美的姐妹  尤其是盖尔
in all of Withering Wharf, especially Gayle.
堪称完美
She was what you'd call a ten.
她有一个差不多美的妹妹  蒂娜
She had an almost equally beautiful sister, Tina.
蒂娜  第二美  比第二美还美一点
She was like a nine. Nine and a half, maybe.
还有尤吉妮亚和露易莎
Also there was Eugenia and Louisa, but they were
不过她们不是很重要  也没什么意思
less important and not that much fun in general.
虽然盖尔有闭月羞花之貌
Though Gayle was extremely beautiful,
她本人却很羞涩
she was also extremely shy.
盖尔  能把面包递给我吗
Gayle, could you please pass me the bread?
对不起  不行  我不好意思
Sorry. I can't. I'm too shy.
四姐妹很穷  家徒四壁
And the sisters were poor. Very, very poor.
我的衣服都破得惨不忍睹了
My petticoats are unspeakable!
姐妹们以为人补衣为生
The sisters got by as seamstresses,
主要缝补士兵裤子屁股那块儿
sewing the butts back on to soldiers' pants
在战场留下的破洞
when they were shot off in battle.
蒂娜渴望嫁给小吉米勋爵
Tina longed to marry Lord Jimmy Jr.,
他的屁股在战场幸免于难
whose butt had been spared in battle,
但根据法律  蒂娜要等大姐
but according to the law of the land, she couldn't do so
盖尔先结婚后  她才能结婚
until her eldest sister Gayle was married first.
这么多沦陷的屁股
So many fallen butts.
这战争怎么还不到头
Why for not can there be an end to this war?
至少我们还能期待一下有钱人舞会
At least we have the Rich Man's Ball to look forward to.
不去
Pass.
亲爱的妹妹  我不能去舞会
Oh, dear sister. I cannot go to the ball.
我太害羞了
I'm far too shy.
可是姐姐  如果你不结婚
But, sister, until you marry,
我们就都不能结婚了
none of us can marry, either.
我要办婚礼  但我要求把结婚蛋糕
I want a wedding! But instead of a wedding cake,
换成纸杯蛋糕
I want to get a bunch of cupcakes
因为我们生活在很久很久以前
because it's a long time ago,
在这时代这个想法还很有创意
so that idea is still good!
但我怕我太害羞
I am afraid I'm far too shy.
会让你们因为我孤独终老
We're all going to die alone because of me.
不要生我的气  好吗
Don't be mad, though, 'kay?
那一晚  蒂娜决定
That was the night that Tina decided
要为盖尔找一位伴侣
she had to find a match for Gayle.
没几天就要到舞会了
It was mere days before the Rich Man's Ball,
蒂娜要抓紧时间找到盖尔的白马王子
and so Tina had to find Gayle a suitor and with haste.
蒂娜把她能想到的黄金单身汉都想了一遍
Tina tried every eligible bachelor she could think of,
但不幸的是  她只能想到一位
but unfortunately she could only think of one.
-铁匠西奥多  -谢谢
- Theodore the blacksmith. - Thank you.
-这是什么  -杯子
- What do you call this thing? - It's a cup.
-再说一遍  好神奇  -杯子
- Say it again. It's amazing. - A cup.
-你以前没见过杯子吗  -没有
- You've never seen a cup before? - Nope.
我直接把头伸进河里喝水
I drink by sticking my head in the river.
-这又是什么  -什么是什么
- And what's this? - What's what?
这把我们围住的东西
This thing all around us.
-你是说房子  -是什么
- A house? - How are you saying that?
-房纸  -不  房子  房子
- House? - No, house. House. How-use. How-use.
-房子  天  我去  -房纸  太快了
- House. House. Oh, God.  - How-use. So quick.
那这个  这个
And what about... what about...
那  那  那
what about... what about... what about...
可惜的是  盖尔没能动心
But alas, Gayle's heart remained empty.
直到他的出现
Until he showed up.
我的马在你们的屋前累瘫了
My horse broke down in front of your cottage.
我想借一下老式水笔和纸
May I use your old-fashioned ink pens and paper
写信通知我的家人和朋友我不能按时到了
to alert my family and friends to my delay?
我会和我的仆人一起去送信
Then I will send the letters with my servant,
那样他们就能在我
and my family will receive the letters
到达的最后一刻之前收到信了
right before I get there.
这套系统很完善
It's a pretty good system.
没问题  先生
Of course, sir...
鲍勃  贝尔彻
Sir Bob. Belcher.
贝尔彻汉堡家族财产的继承人
Lord and heir to the Belcher Burger fortune.
天哪  是鲍勃
Oh, my God, that's Bob.
什么  你就是主办
Why, you're the lord throwing
有钱人舞会的人  是吗
the Rich Man's Ball, are you not?
这位是
And who is this?
你的脚踝  美极了
Your ankles are... great.
她叫盖尔  至今未婚
Her name is Gayle, and she's not married.
如果你喜欢她的脚踝
And if you like her ankles,
你应该看看她的小腿
you should see her shins.
她的小腿有好几英寸长
Her shins go on for inches.
你最好别让我的鲍勃娶了盖尔  小姐
You better not be marrying my Bob off to Gayle, little missy.
让我念完  好吗
Just let me finish, okay?
好吧  盖尔  希望能在舞会上见到你
Well, Gayle, I hope I shall see you at mine ball.
我应该  扶她起来吗
Should I, uh, pick her up?
不用了  我们通常都让她这样躺着
Nah, we usually just let her sleep there when that happens.
等下  她着火了
Oh. Wait. No, she's on fire.
快把她挪开
Let's move her.
舞会这天到了
The date of the ball had arrived.
镇上每个人都来了
Everyone from town was there.
镇上的人都来了
Everyone from town is here.
连勋爵阿尔比诺・肯都来了  肯
Even Lord Ken the albino! Ken!
我等不及见到鲍勃先生了
Oh, I can't wait to see Sir Bob!
是啊  玩得开心
Yeah. Have fun with that.
我要去把我的束身衣塞满薄饼
I'm gonna go put a bunch of crumpets down my corset.
我要带着满嘴的食物离开
Gonna leave this place with a month's worth of food.
你好  盖尔
Hello, Gayle.
你腰上那可爱的带子是什么
What is that lovely sash about your waist?
我叫它腰包
I call it a fanny pack.
很迷人的
It's very fetching.
你好  蒂娜小姐  你好
Hi, Lady Tina. Hi.
我希望你喜欢当代男孩组合的表演
I hope you like the band Boys Fore the Present Tyme.
他们在城里很有人气
They are very popular in the city.
来  跳支舞吧
Come, let's dance.
他们在演奏小细臀
They're playing the Heinie Liney.
开什么玩笑  蒂娜
Tina, seriously?
老爸  拜托  马上结尾了
Dad, please! I'm almost done.
鲍勃先生和盖尔跳了一晚上
Sir Bob and Gayle danced together all evening.
他们的眼睛和屁股
They couldn't take their eyes,
都不曾离开对方
or butts, off of each other.
我性感的未婚夫去哪了
Where's my sexy fiance?!
他在哪呢
Where is he?!
鲍勃
Bob!
我在这  嗨  亲爱的
here I am. Uh, hi... honey.
真不敢相信你办舞会没喊我
I can't believe you'd have a ball without me,
我是即将包养你的
your loud, rude, American wife-to-be
大嗓门粗暴美国未婚妻啊
that you're marrying for money!
过来  给我亲一个
Come here! Give me a kiss!
盖尔为鲍勃先生无比心碎
Gayle was so heartbroken over Sir Bob
病得上吐下泻
that she fell deathly ill with pooping cough.
她的姐妹们试了所有办法想让她好起来
Her sisters tried everything to bring her back to health.
-水蛭疗法  -好吃
- Leeches. - Yum!
沙滩疗法
Beaches.
尖叫疗法
Screeches.
-起来  -别装病了
- Wake up! - Stop being sick!
但都没有效果
But nothing worked.
他们喊来了牧师送她最后一程
They called the vicar to come give her last rites.
我是牧师   斯科特・巴库拉
I'm the vicar, Scott Bakula.
你好啊  我好像忽然好多了
Well, hello! I'm feeling much better all of a sudden.
好吧  让我在你嘴里祈个祷
Oh, good. Well, let me whisper a prayer into your mouth.
然后他们穿越到了未来
Then they Quantum Leapt into the future
和蒂娜还有小吉米来了场双人婚礼
to the day of their double wedding with Tina and Jimmy Jr.,
从此过上了幸福的生活
and they all lived happily ever after.
鲍勃先生和琳达也结婚了
And Sir Bob and Linda were also married,
他们生了个有尾巴的小孩
and then they had a baby with a tail
因为他们是近亲  完结
because they were cousins. The end.
太好了
That was so good!
我都能感到斯科特・巴库拉在我嘴里祈祷
I could feel Scott Bakula's kiss whispers in my mouth!
-嘴祷  -不咋样
- Kisspers! - I've heard better.
你爸和我才不是近亲
And your father and I are not cousins.
据我们所知
That we know of.
你赢了  蒂娜
You win, Tina.
还是让吉恩赢呢
Oh! Or should Gene win?
天哪  真难抉择
Oh, gosh, this is tough.
我想你忘了什么
I think you're forgetting something.
好吧  你来吧
Oh, right. Okay, go ahead.
我把它称作"盖尔的游戏"
I call it "Gayle of Thrones."
慢慢来  各位
Pace yourselves, guys.
要吸冷气的地方还多着呢
You're gonna want to save your gasps.
请听猫特罗斯国女王陛下的故事
Behold the tale of Queen Gayle of Catsteros.
她是九大猫国中
She was the most powerful woman
最强大的女人
in all of the nine Cat-life kingdoms,
是世上仅剩不多的几只猫龙的女主人
and mistress of the world's only cat dragons.
猫特罗斯的臣民们
People of Catsteros,
尽情的吃喝喵喵叫吧
please eat, drink and be meowy!
尊敬的殿下  喵
Your Royal Highness... meow...
有从小波西米亚国来的访客
visitors from the kingdom of Litter Boxia!
盖尔女王  我们代你姐姐
Lady Gayle, we come on behalf of your sister,
小波西米亚国的琳达瑞恩而来
Lindaryen of Litter Boxia,
代她送上一份大礼
to present you with a gift in her absence.
礼  真难得
A gift? I'm surprised.
她一直很嫉妒我
She's always been jealous of me
因为我有猫龙
because I have cat dragons,
又不是个暴躁的老巫婆
and I'm not a cranky old hag.
好吧  她没提过这个
Oh, well, she didn't mention that.
现在  请允许我介绍  这位
And now, may I present, this guy!
我是无屁家族的吉恩
I'm Gene from the House of the Unfarting.
女王殿下  我是个魔术师
My Queen, I am a warlock.
如果我消失了  就请检查下你的后面
If I disappear, just check your rear.
别担心
But don't worry.
我总会出现的
I always turn up.
但永远不是在原处
Just never where you left me!
有意思
Oh, impressive.
他本来在那儿  喵
He was over there... meow...
现在又在那了  喵
and now he's over here. Meow.
我都糊涂了
I'm befuddled.
我喜欢你的猫龙
I love your cat dragons!
我会用货车把他们带走
I'll take them in my wagon.
什么  我检查过后面了
Wha? I'm checking my rear!
他不在  他带走了我的猫龙
He's not there! And he took my cat dragons!
我在这
Here I am.
-开个玩笑  -不
- Just kidding. - No!
我的猫龙被抓走了
My cat dragons are gone.
我必须去救他们
I must go get them.
他们是我的孩子
They are my children.
他们是喝我的奶长大的
They've suckled at my teats!
请让我们最勇敢的骑士与你同行
At least let our bravest knight go with you
助您一臂之力  喵
to assist Your Grace. Meow.
盖尔女王
My Lady Gayle.
露易丝骑士  这是我自己的战斗
Knight Louise, this is my fight.
我不能拿你的生命冒险
I cannot risk your life.
但我想  况且我真的很讨厌琳达瑞恩
But I can. Plus, I really dislike Lindaryen.
她是个因为孩子开恶作剧玩笑
She's a tyrant who punishes children unjustly
就乱惩罚他们的暴君
for doing hilarious pranks.
我以我的忠心和飞掌向你发誓
I swear my service and my steel to you.
保加利亚飞掌
The Burgarean Slapper!
我们启程吧
Let us be off.
没了我和我的奶水
My cat dragons are probably very confused
我的猫龙肯定会很恐慌
without me and my breast milk.
猫特罗斯的臣民们
People of Catsteros,
留在这  坚持住
remain here, remain strong.
我会带着龙回来的
I will return with our dragons!
到时我将给你们每个人喂奶
And then I shall breast-feed all of you!
于是他们向小波西米亚启程
And so they set off for Litter Boxia,
一路上打败了很多敌人
fighting their many enemies along the way.
他们先后被格林姆沃德的特尔斯
They were held prisoner by Theus of Grimward,
格林贾木德的泰尼斯和格林金特的泰比思俘虏
Thannis of Grinjammed, and Thambis of Gramjimnt.
但每次都幸运逃脱
But each time, they escaped.
那儿就是小波西米亚的大门了  女王陛下
There are the gates of Litter Boxia, My Queen.
真的好臭呢
It really stinks here.
是的  小波西米亚已经很久没打扫过了
Yes, Litter Boxia has not been cleaned in many moons.
而就在小波西米亚之外
And outside of Litter Boxia,
有九个猫国中
the most dreaded monsters
最令人闻之色变的野兽
in all of the Nine Cat-Life Kingdoms.
听  女王  前面有声音
Hark, my lady. A sound ahead.
是什么  听起来超无趣
What is it? It sounds really boring.
是大白话痨怪
It's a White Talker!
快捂住耳朵  他们的话
Cover your ears, or they will literally
会无趣到让你失去神智的
bore you into a deathlike slumber.
我想尽办法想把我内裤上
I tried everything to get that barbecue
那滴烧烤油擦掉
stain out of my underpants.
五金店最好的停车地点
The best place to park at the hardware store
多半就是停车场了
is probably the parking lot.
我好痒  天呐
Oh, I have an itch. Oh. Oh, God. Oh, it...
-真的好痒  好想挠一挠  -别挠
- Oh, it's so itchy. Oh, I got to itch it. - Don't itch it!
我忍不了了
Oh, I can't wait any longer!
-千万别把手拿开  -我想挠
- Do not take your hands off your ears!  - I got to itch it.
-女王陛下  不要啊  -老天
- My lady, no! - Oh, God!
不  他太强大了
Oh, no. He got me.
简直太无趣了
So boring.
我快被无聊死了
I'm... so bored.
露易丝
Louise...!
你是谁
Who goes there?
是我  盖尔  猫特罗斯国的女王
It is I, Gayle, Queen of Catsteros.
我来找我姐姐琳达瑞恩
I seek my sister Lindaryen.
她偷了我的龙
She has stolen my dragons.
哦  好吧
Oh. Okay.
你就是盖尔啊  好吧
So you're Gayle. Okay.
进去吧
Just go in or whatever. Hi.
各位  听我唱
Everyone, listen to me sing!
-鲍勃铎尔  -盖尔
- Bobdor. - Gayle!
姐姐  没想到我会来吧
Sister. Surprised to see me?
才没有  我早知道你会来
Not at all! I knew you'd come,
我还知道等你来我会取了你的性命
and I knew when you did I'd get rid of you once and for all!
我要跟你  决斗
I challenge you... to a duel.
以性命决斗吗
To the death?
没错  但我们还是
Yes! But let's do that thing
先各自选两个代表
where we pick someone to represent us
替我们出战
and fight in our honor,
为我们死吧
and then die in our place, right?
好主意
Oh, good idea.
我选  莫特塔因
I choose The Mort-tain!
好吧
Oh, okay.
等我下
Hang on.
不好意思了  露易丝  我现在需要你
Sorry to do this, Louise, but I need you.
怎么  怎么回事
What-What's going on?
我要你赌上性命代替我跟我姐姐决斗
I need you to fight for me in a duel to the death.
-好啊  -废话少说
- Oh! Good. -Enough talk!
开始决斗吧
Let the duel commence!
但为了让这场比赛更有趣
But let's make this fight a little more interesting.
小心别掉进
Be careful not to fall
我嗷嗷待哺的瓷宝宝坑里咯
into my pit of ravenous porcelain babies.
我已经好几天没喂他们了
They haven't been fed in days.
饥辘肠肠
So hungry.
感谢参与  大个子
Thanks for playing, big guy.
我去  不该开那个的
Oh, crap. Shouldn't have done that.
好吧  你光明正大地打败了我
Well, you beat me fair and square,
但我还是要杀了你
but I'm gonna kill you anyway.
鲍勃铎尔  把她们扔进坑里
Bobdor, throw 'em into the pit.
鲍勃铎尔
Bobdor.
你到底是要做不要做
Does that mean yes or no?
-你永远只会说那一个词  -鲍勃铎尔
- 'Cause it's the only thing you ever say. - Bobdor.
并没有更好
Yeah, that doesn't help.
我得重新找个呆瓜
I got to get a new fool.
这次找个瘦点的
Maybe somebody thinner.
我想要性感一点的
I want somebody hot.
你  你要干嘛
What-what are you doing?
我的宝宝在吃我
My babies are eating me!
坏宝宝  走开
Oh, bad babies! Down!
谢谢你  鲍勃铎尔
Thank you, Bobdor.
等我回到猫特罗斯国
I'll breast-feed you first
会先给你喂奶
when we get back to Catsteros.
好了  各位  我们回家了
All right, everybody, let's go home.
斯科特・巴库拉
Scott Bakula?!
你从哪儿冒出来的
Where did you come from?
那重要吗
Does it really matter?
鲍勃铎尔电灯泡  拜拜
Bobdor third wheel. Bye-bye.
鲍勃铎尔
Bobdor!
剧终
The end.
露易丝  你没看过《权利的游戏》吧
Louise, you haven't watched Game of Thrones, right?
没有  啥游戏
No. Game of what?
我都不知道你在说啥
I don't know what you're talking about.
-露易丝  太棒了  -那是
- Oh, Louise, that was so good. - Yup.
你们真是我的好侄子好侄女
You're just all such wonderful nieces and nephews.
我不需要史黛西了
I don't need Stacy.
你们让我看到  我天赋异禀
You've shown me that I'm talented
万人疼爱  无人能敌
and lovable and strong...
嗨  盖尔
Hey, Gayle.
还要约会吗
Still up for that date?
我的急事儿取消了
My emergency canceled.
史黛西  你怎么知道我在这儿
Stacy! How'd you find me?
你在我公司  我家  和我妈那儿
All those messages you left me at work and at home
都留了纸条告诉我你的行踪
and at my mother's telling me where you were going.
哦  对
Oh. Oh, yeah.
好咧  我们走吧
Okay, let's get out of here!
拜  孩子们
Bye, kids.
-别啊  -别啊
- No! - No!
我去
Son of a bitch!
老妈  别这样  你真的要禁我们足吗
Mom, come on. Are we really still grounded?
我们是闹着玩儿的
We were just trying to be funny.
是啊  我们就想让你开怀一笑
Yeah. We tried to make you laugh,
但没想到你让大家都笑了
but instead, you made the world laugh.
听起来是挺好笑的
It did sound kind of funny.
五小时前
老妈  能买点冰淇淋吗
Mom, uh, can we get some ice cream?
-是啊  那儿的冰柜里有  -行啊
- Yeah. From that case right there. - Yeah!
冰淇淋  好好吃的样子  好主意姑娘们
Ice cream. Yummy. Good idea, girls.
冰柜怪人
Freezer Frankenstein!
琳  你倒在了一堆卫生棉上  还放了个屁
Lin, you fell into a pile of maxi pads, and you farted.
确实很好笑
It's pretty funny.
一点都不好笑
It wasn't funny!
别人都在看我笑话
Everyone laughed at me.
-是的  -没错  -没错
- Yeah. - Yup. - Yup.
我还不得不把那些卫生棉都买回家
And then I had to buy all those maxi pads.
那些得好久才能用完呢
it's gonna take me weeks to get through those!
而且他们把包递给我的时候我又放了个屁
And then I farted again when they handed me my bags.
老妈  简直太完美了  你不觉得吗
Mom, it was perfect. Don't you see?
我真为你自豪
I'm proud of you!
你的屁深入我们心  老妈
You farted your way into our hearts, Mom.
好吧  是  是很好笑
Okay. It was... it was funny.
确实很好笑
It was funny.
所以你不禁我们足咯
So, we aren't grounded anymore?
听着  你们今晚还是要禁足
Tell you what. You're grounded for tonight,
在家陪我看电视
and you all have to watch TV with me.
行  总算有事做了
All right, it's something.
我看什么你们就得看什么
And we're gonna watch whatever I want,
我们还要像三明治一样依偎在一起
and we're gonna be a big snuggle sandwich.
我要做中间的奶酪
I'm the cheese, right in the middle,
人人都爱我
and everyone likes me!
等等  你们去哪儿
Wait, where are you going?
还没关门呢
We're not closed.
-还有几小时才打烊呢  -回见  老爸
- We-we don't close for hours. - Bye, Dad!
等等等等等  别关...
Wai-wai-wai-wait. Don't close the d...
门关了
They closed the door.
我应该答应盖尔的
I should have gone with Gayle.